<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Pages on Hugo Bootstrap Theme</title><link>https://filipecarneiro.github.io/hugo-bootstrap-theme/pages/</link><description>Recent content in Pages on Hugo Bootstrap Theme</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-US</language><atom:link href="https://filipecarneiro.github.io/hugo-bootstrap-theme/pages/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Bootstrap Components ✨</title><link>https://filipecarneiro.github.io/hugo-bootstrap-theme/pages/bootstrap-components/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://filipecarneiro.github.io/hugo-bootstrap-theme/pages/bootstrap-components/</guid><description>Bootstrap Components Bootstrap is bundled with tens of components that can be reused to provide a good user experience and user interactions in a web page.
Accordion Accordion Item #1 This is the first item's accordion body. It is shown by default, until the collapse plugin adds the appropriate classes that we use to style each element. These classes control the overall appearance, as well as the showing and hiding via CSS transitions.</description></item><item><title>Markdown Cheat Sheet Ⓜ️⬇️</title><link>https://filipecarneiro.github.io/hugo-bootstrap-theme/pages/markdown-cheat-sheet/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://filipecarneiro.github.io/hugo-bootstrap-theme/pages/markdown-cheat-sheet/</guid><description>Markdown Cheat Sheet Hugo has excellent Markdown support out of the box. By default, Hugo uses the Goldmark Markdown processor which is fully CommonMark-compliant. See the configuration instructions to learn more about the extensions you can configure.
Overview You can refer to the table below for an overview of basic markdown syntax:
TASK MARKDOWN SYNTAX Heading 1 # Heading 2 ## Heading 3 ### Italics *italics* Bold **Bold** Strike ~~strike~~ Blockquote &amp;gt; Links [link name](https://link.</description></item><item><title>Security Best Practices 🔒</title><link>https://filipecarneiro.github.io/hugo-bootstrap-theme/pages/security-best-practices/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://filipecarneiro.github.io/hugo-bootstrap-theme/pages/security-best-practices/</guid><description>Security Best Practices Improve code health of your web page following these best practices.
Use HTTPS All websites should be protected with HTTPS, even ones that don&amp;rsquo;t handle sensitive data. HTTPS prevents intruders from tampering with or passively listening in on the communications between your site and your users.
External Links When you link to a page on another site using the target=&amp;quot;_blank&amp;quot; attribute, you can expose your site to performance and security issues:</description></item></channel></rss>